A Guide to the John D. Rockefeller 3rd papers, Associates, Raymond A. LaMontagne papers FA783
Rockefeller Archive Center
John D. Rockefeller 3rd papers, Associates, Raymond A. LaMontagne papers
1959, 1961-1969, 1973-1974
Rockefeller Archive Center
LaMontagne, Ray
Rockefeller, John D. III (John Davison), 1906-1978
FA783
2.6 Cubic Feet 6 document boxes.
Scope and Contents
Types of records include: correspondence, brochures and pamphlets, minutes, and newspaper articles.
Arrangement
As received.
Conditions Governing Access
Collection is open for research. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
LaMontagne, Ray; Rockefeller, John D. III (John Davison), 1906-1978
- Agricultural Development Council, Inc., 1962, 1964-1968 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Population, Conferences, Miscellaneous, Aspen & White House Conferences, 1964-1967 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Population, General, 1961, 1964-1968 (Box 1, Folder 3-4)
- Population, International Conference on Abortion, Washington, D. C., 1967 September 6-8 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Population, International Conference on Family Planning Programs, Geneva, 1965 August 23-27, 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Population, International Conference of International Planned Parenthood Foundation, Santiago, Chile, 1967 April 9-15, 1966-1968 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Population, Cooperation Year Conference, White House Conference on International Cooperation, 1965 November 29, 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Population, Long Range Planning Committee of Planned Parenthood-World Population, Bermuda, 1968 March 9-12, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Population, National Conference on Family planning, Washington, D. C., 1966 May 5-6 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Population, Next Steps, 1959, 1964-1966 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Population, Planned Parenthood, 1967-1969 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Population, Planned Parenthood, Chicago Area, 1964, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Population, Planned Parenthood of New York City, Fundraising and Chairman, 1966-1968 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Population, Planned Parenthood of New York City, Miscellaneous Correspondence, Since the Merger of the Affiliates 1966 November 28, 1966-1968 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Population, Planned Parenthood of New York City, Minutes of Meetings, Board, Nominating Committee & Financial Information, 1966-1968 (Box 3, Folder 16-17)
- Population, Planned Parenthood of New York City, Minutes/Meetings, Executive Committee, 1966-1968 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Population, Planned Parenthood of New York City, Pre-Merger of New York City Affiliates, 1965-1966 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Population, Pope's Visit, 1964-1968 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Population, Population Council, 1961-1969 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Population, Population Crisis Committee, Draper & Victor Fund, 1965-1968 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Population, Population Research and Development, Inc., 1962-1964 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Population, Postpartum Program, 1965, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Population, Southeast Asia Development Advisory Group (SEDAG), 1967 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Population, "Summit" Meeting, 1966 January 7, 1965-1966 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Population, United States Government, 1964-1967 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Population, University of Michigan, Fertility and Family Planning: World View, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Population, World Leaders' Statements, Miscellaneous, 1959, 1965-1968, 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 29-30)
- Population, World Leaders' Statement, 1st Group, A-C, 1966-1968 (Box 5, Folder 31)
- Population, World Leaders' Statement, 1st Group, F-J, 1966-1968 (Box 5, Folder 32)
- Population, World Leaders' Statement, 1st Group, K-P, 1966-1968 (Box 5, Folder 33)
- Population, World Leaders' Statement, 1st Group, S-Y, 1966-1968 (Box 5, Folder 34)
- Population, World Leaders' Statement, 2nd Group, A-E, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 35)
- Population, World Leaders' Statement, 2nd Group, I-U, 1964-1968 (Box 6, Folder 36)
- Population, World Leaders' Statement, 3rd Group, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 37)
- Population, World Leaders' Statement, 4th Group, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 38)
- Population, World Leaders' Statement, 5th Group, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 39)
- Population, World Leaders' Statement, United Nations Ceremony, Statements & Publicity, 1966-1968 (Box 6, Folder 40)